[{"question":"which object is smaller?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"What is the material of the large cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"Dirt"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"Blueunknown"}],"answer":1},{"question":"How many cubes there?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"4"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object has lower density?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Is the medium RedUnknown cube heavier than the large BlueUnknown cube?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger friction?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which object has larger restitution?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which quadrant will the large BlueUnknown cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":2},{"question":"Which quadrant will the medium marble cube be in when it finally stops moving ?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"\u2160"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"\u2161"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"\u2162"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"\u2163"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which object will stop moving earlier?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The medium marble cube"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Which object will stop moving first?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium marble cube travel to quadrant \u2160?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will there a collision in the quadrant \u2161?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"How many collisions will happen between objects?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"<=3"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":">3"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the medium RedUnknown cube collide more than once?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium RedUnknown cube collide with the medium marble cube in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0},{"question":"Will the medium RedUnknown cube collide with the wall in this video?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Which objects is the first collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube and the medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The wall and the medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The wall and the large blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium marble cube and the large blueunknown cube"}],"answer":3},{"question":"Which objects is the last collision?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"The wall and the large blueunknown cube"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"The large blueunknown cube and the medium redunknown cube"},{"choice_id":2,"choice":"The medium marble cube and the wall"},{"choice_id":3,"choice":"The medium redunknown cube and the medium marble cube"}],"answer":1},{"question":"Will the large BlueUnknown cube collide with other objects after it stops moving?","option":[{"choice_id":0,"choice":"yes"},{"choice_id":1,"choice":"no"}],"answer":0}]